Allen

Personal Information

Name: Yilun Wu

Phone: 0212725003

Visa type: Work Visa - Post-study - Open

Expires: 03/09/2023

E-Mail: allenshielder1994@outlook.com

Career Objective

Although as a software engineer with over 2 years of work experience, I still have great enthusiasm for different sorts of technologies. I also have excellent communication and collaboration skills, which means I can effectively spread complex technical concepts to non-technical clients and my team members. I always keep a positive side to the work and can work independently. I eagerly expect to join your group.

Summary& Skills

- Complex enterprise systems (Pepsi and Huawei) support experience
- Master's Degree in Computer Engineering.
- Good knowledge of Salesforce Lightning App Builder.
- Good knowledge of Salesforce Admin(Flow, Approval, and Permission)
- Good knowledge of Salesforce Developer(Apex, LWC, SOQL, and Trigger).
- Good knowledge of Salesforce DevOps(Azure, Jenkins, and Copado).
- Good knowledge of .NET(C#).
- Good knowledge of JavaScript, Html and CSS.
- Good knowledge of SQL.
- Ability to work in team collaboration or independently.
- Ability to work under pressure.
- Ability to troubleshoot complex software and hardware issues
- · Ability to build trusting relationships with clients and colleagues
- Have excellent communication skills (both written and verbal).

Project Experience

xFusion

- **Situation:** xFusion is Huawei's project. Huawei plans to rebuild the CRM and PRM systems via Salesforce. They also plan to update CRM and PRM systems because of new transactions.
- **Task:** Development of partial feature in partnership policy modules; The development of the partner certification module; Data model design; Deployment and release of the xFusion system.
- Action: Developed front-end of PRM and CRM system using LWC(JavaScript); The developed back-end of PRM system using Apex, Flow, and Approval; Wrote technical documentation; Deployed whole system using PowerShell via Azure; Provided DevOps tutorial to clients and PwC China.

• **Result:** Received high comments from clients. The project was released and deployed successfully.

LATAM (Dynamo 2.0 and Hercules)

- **Situation:** The client is Pepsi Group. Pepsi's business in Latin America has changed, and they also plan to update the whole system structure.
- **Task:** Modify configuration and corresponding code in Salesforce; Development back-end of a mobile App; Test connection between SAP and Salesforce; Write unit test code.
- Action: Modified configuration and corresponding Apex programs; the Developed back-end of the App in Salesforce Lightning App Builder using Apex; Monitored received data from SAP and log; Wrote system architecture documentation; Wrote test class to improve coverage.
- **Result:** Completed the project requirement. The system architecture diagram has greatly helped SAP developers and PwC onshore teams.

Block 1

- **Situation:** The Financial Project in Hong Kong. The client is required to add new features in Service Now and test the connection between the new-built server and Service Now.
- Task: Modification of front-end and back-end; Development of file antivirus and management system; Connect test between the new server and Service Now.
- **Action:** Updated front-end and back-end of Service Now using JavaScript; Developed new feature using Node JS; Used Postman to debug the REST API with new server.
- Result: Complete customer's requirements and new features released successfully.

Soda Express and Soda Go

- **Situation:** To improve the quality and reduce the price of food delivery in New Zealand. The project created a delivery app for the customers and a driver app for the drivers.
- Task: Design and Development of APP; Development of Management system; SQL Design; REST API test between App and back-end of the management system.
- Action: Developed APPs using Flutter; Developed and deployed management systems using front-end and back-end technologies such as JavaScript, HTML, CSS, ASP.NET(C#), and Salesforce; Designed a database with MySQL; Deployed the whole system using Jenkins.
- **Result:** Mobile App (IOS and Android version) and management system were released successfully; The number of users grew after one month of product launch.

Work History

Sr Software Engineer | PwC | Remote | 08/2021- 02/2023

- Salesforce Developer
- DevOps(Azure, Jenkins, and Copado)
- Quality Analysis & Tester

Technical Leader | LoveLive Ltd(Self -Entrepreneurial) | New Zealand | 12/2019-03/2021

- Full stack Developer(Flutter, Salesforce, C#, and MySQL)
- DevOps(Jenkins)
- Technical Support

Educational Background

Master of Engineering | Massey University | 08/2019-11/2020

• Major: Electronic and Computer Engineering